<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: meetings | SGVHAK]]></title>
  <link href="http://sgvhak.github.com/blog/categories/meetings/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sgvhak.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-01-29T14:45:29-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://sgvhak.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming Meetings]]></title>
    <link href="http://sgvhak.github.com/blog/2012/10/15/upcoming-meetings/"/>
    <updated>2012-10-15T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sgvhak.github.com/blog/2012/10/15/upcoming-meetings</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We are planning to meet on November 1st. We are awaiting a room confirmation. Watch this space or join the mailing list for updates.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[SGVHAK Kickoff]]></title>
    <link href="http://sgvhak.github.com/blog/2012/09/20/raspberry-pi-etc-sig/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-20T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sgvhak.github.com/blog/2012/09/20/raspberry-pi-etc-sig</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><em>If you are interested in the group, please sign up for the <a href="http://sgvhak.net/mailman/listinfo/hak" title="SGVHAK Mailing List Sign Up">SGVHAK mailing list</a>. We will continue to crosspost announcements to the SGVLUG mailing list. We are in the process of setting up a website or subpage.</em></p>

<p>Do you like working on hardware projects?  Did you just get a Raspberry Pi/Arduino/Kinect with the intentions of doing something cool?  Did you wish that there was a local meetup group where you can meet up with like-minded folks and actually make progress with your projects?</p>

<p>Come to our kickoff meeting on Thursday to discuss starting up this special interest group.  Connect with your fellow hardware geeks and share some of the projects you've been working on. And if we can decide on a name for the SIG, we can set up things like a mailing list, website, and wiki.</p>

<p>We have been kindly granted access to a room at Caltech for this meeting only.  It is a small classroom with about 30 student desks and a teacher desk.  We will have access to a projector and power.  There is an open wireless network.</p>

<p>Date: Thursday, September 20, 2012 @ 7 pm <br/>
Location: Caltech - Downs 119</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
